carbon38.com 2017-03-17

# Privacy Policy

### Carbon38 Privacy Policy

Effective as of April 1, 2012

Your privacy, and the privacy of all users of Carbon38 (“Carbon38 ”), is important to us. Carbon38 is committed to protecting your privacy online. Accordingly, Carbon38 has developed this privacy policy that describes the data we collect, how we use it, and with whom we share it (“Privacy Policy”). This Privacy Policy sets forth the policies and procedures of personally identifiable information received from users of the Service, including but not limited to the website at www.carbon38.com and the mobile applications created by Carbon38 (collectively, the “Carbon38 Service” or “Service”). This Privacy Policy is applicable to all site visitors, registered users, and all other users of the Service.

The terms “We”, “Us”, and “Carbon38 ” refer to the Carbon38 Service. The terms “You” and “Your” refer to you, as a visitor or user of the Service. By using the Service, you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy, as amended from time to time. Further, you acknowledge that this Privacy Policy is part of our Terms of Service (“TOS”), which is incorporated by reference, and by accessing or using the Service, you agree to be bound by all of its terms and conditions. If you do not agree to these terms, and the terms and conditions in our TOS, please do not access or use the Service.

### Personal Information We Collect and Use:

  * Personal Information: When registering as a user to the Service, we receive and store information you enter or provide to us in any other way. The types of personal information collected may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, URL, phone number, Twitter, Google Plus and/or Facebook usernames, location, use information regarding your use of the Service, browser information, and any other data that is tied to such information (collectively, the “Personal Information”). If your location settings are active, we automatically receive your location when you use the Service. The Personal Information you provide is used for such purposes as allowing you to set up a user account and profile that can be used to interact with other users through the Service, improving the content of the Service, customizing the advertising and content you see, and communicating with you about specials and new features. We may also draw upon this Personal Information in order to adapt the Services of our community to your needs, to research the effectiveness of our network and Services, and to develop new tools for the community.
  * Profiles: “Public Content” refers to information that you submit or post to the Service for public display, such as photos, comments, reviews, and your public profile information.
  * Information Collected Automatically: When you use the Service, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser or mobile platform, including your location, IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested. This data is treated as non-Personal Information, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law. We only use this data in aggregate form to perform statistical analyses on user behavior and characteristics. We may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our customers, collectively, use our site, so that our partners may also understand how often people use their services and the Service.

### How My Information Is Shared:

Personal Information about our users is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information to anyone. We may share your Personal Information with third parties with your permission or as permitted in our TOS. The third parties may in turn publicly display or publish the Public Content in connection with their own website and media platforms.

We provide some of our services through affiliates, service providers, partners and other third parties. We, and our service partners, may use your personal information to operate our sites and to deliver their services. These affiliates and third party service providers are not permitted to use personal information for any purposes other than to complete the order, assist you in participating in the particular service and communicating with you. We will encourage our service partners to adopt and post privacy policies. However, the use of your personal information by our service partners is governed by the privacy policies of those service partners, and is not subject to our control.

We may disclose information in the aggregate to third parties relating to user behavior in connection with actual or prospective business relationships with those third parties, such as advertisers and content distributors. For example, we may disclose the number of users that have been exposed to, or clicked on, advertising banners.

In the future, we may use third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Service. These companies may use information about your Public Content (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) and activity related to your use of the Service to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

One of the primary reasons people use Carbon38 is to connect with other users and service providers. Information such as your name and photo, location, list of friends, and the comments you write is shared with the Carbon38 community. Individuals reading this information may use it or disclose it to other individuals or entities without our control and without your knowledge. We therefore urge you to think carefully about including any specific information you may deem private in comments or other content (location or otherwise) that you create in the Service.

Law Enforcement and Protection. We may disclose your Personal Information to third parties in a good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) take action regarding suspected illegal activities; (b) enforce or apply our TOS and Privacy Policy; (c) comply with legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order; or (d) protect our rights, reputation, and property, or that of our users, affiliates, or the public. Please note that we are not required to question or contest the validity of any search warrant, subpoena or other similar governmental request that we receive.

Invite Friends and Contacts. You may choose to provide us with another person's e-mail address or social network profile information so that person may be invited to create an account on this site and become your friend. We use this information to contact and, if necessary, remind that person about the invitation. By providing us with another person's e-mail address, you represent to us that you have obtained the consent of the person concerned with respect to such disclosure to us of their Personal Information. We may disclose such information if required to do so in order to comply with legal process, as described above.

Business Transfers If Carbon38 or substantially all of its assets are acquired, or in the unlikely event that we cease business operations or enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party.

### Cookies and Similar Technologies:

We send cookies to your computer through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages on our site are visited and by how many people. Most browsers have an option for disabling the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting cookies, as well as (depending on your browser software) allow you to decide on acceptance of cookies in a variety of ways.

Ads appearing on the Service may be delivered to users by our advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by us and our service providers and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

We use analytics (and related analytics programs) to better understand who is using the Service, and how people are using it. Analytics uses cookies to collect and store anonymous information such as time of visit, pages visited, time spent on each page of the website, IP address, and type of operating system used. We use this information to improve the Service and make it appealing to as many users as possible.

### Security:

Your account is password protected for your privacy and security. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password, and limiting access to your computer, phone and browser such as signing off after you have finished accessing your account. We use industry standard measures to protect Personal Information. However, we cannot guarantee the security of account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.

The Service may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site, you should read the privacy policy stated on that site. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on the Service.

### International Users:

If you are located outside of the United States, please note that the Service is located on computer servers in the United States. Therefore, your information may be processed and stored in the United States. As a result, United States federal and state governments, courts, or law enforcement or regulatory agencies may be able to obtain disclosure of your information through laws applicable in the United States. Your use of the Service or your submission of any Personal Information to us will constitute your consent to the transfer of your Personal Information outside of your home country, including the United States, which may provide for different data protection rules than in your country.

### Privacy Practices of Third Parties and Third Party Sites:

The Service may contain links to third party websites and applications to which we have no affiliation. Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Other sites accessible through our site via links or service partnerships have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. Please consult each site’s privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. Additionally, other companies may place advertising on our site and may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising through the use of cookies. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect.

### Control of Personal Information:

To the extent you include Personal Information in your Public Content (such as a photo of yourself), third parties may be able to identify you, associate you with your account, and contact you. Please do not include information in your Public Content that you expect to keep private.

Third parties can also associate you with your account using the user search and browse features of the Carbon38 Service, which display your Public Content.

Upon your request, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to close your account, and cease displaying your Public Content on the Service; nevertheless, we may still retain your Personal Information and your Public Content in our systems. Registered users who wish to close their account should contact us.

### Changes To Privacy Policy:

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make material changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement, sending you an email, or updating the Privacy Policy on the site. You are encouraged to review the Privacy Policy from time to time in the event changes have been made. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when they use the Service after such changes have been first posted.

### Questions Or Concerns:

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy using the Service, please send a detailed message to: help@carbon38.com We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.
